arkivmusic.com 2011-12-24

# ArkivMusic | Privacy Policy

**Please Note: By visiting and using the website at**www.ArkivMusic.com **, you are accepting the privacy policies contained in this notification.**

At ArkivMusic.com, we are committed to protecting every customer's privacy. The information we gather on our website is used to process orders and to provide our customers with an optimal shopping experience. We do not share personal customer information with any entity outside of ArkivMusic for any purpose other than as required to process orders, or as required by law. ArkivMusic will never send promotional email unless a customer specifically opts in to receive it. 

ArkivMusic may occasionally send offers through the mail (U.S. Postal Service), on behalf of ourselves or our partners, that we believe will be of interest to our customers. Such mailings are handled by ArkivMusic, and personal customer information is not revealed to our partners. If you do not wish to receive these types of mail offers, you may send an email to service@arkivmusic.com to be removed from our mailing list. 

Information We Collect

To properly and efficiently process your purchases on ArkivMusic.com, we need to collect information to enable order payment and shipments. This includes your credit card number and expiration date, the billing address associated with that credit card, the shipping address for your purchases, and a telephone number to contact you if a package is undeliverable. In addition, we collect your email address so that we can keep you up to date with the status of your orders 

Protecting Your Information   
ArkivMusic takes extraordinary care to handle all of your personal information securely. When you submit information on the ArkivMusic.com website, it is encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer software while being transferred. It is then stored on a server that is behind a firewall, and not connected to the internet. We take the same measures while transmitting your information to a third-party regulated processor for payment authorization and settlement. What About Cookies?

A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier that is transferred to your computer's hard drive through your web browser. A cookie enables our systems to recognize your browser and allows us to keep your session intact on ArkivMusic.com. This means, for example, that we can keep track of items you've place in your shopping cart while you continue to look for other products throughout the site. We will never use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that did not originate from ArkivMusic.com. 

Use of Website by Children

ArkivMusic.com does not sell products to children. If you are under 18 years old, you must be accompanied by a parent or legal guardian to place orders on ArkivMusic.com. 

Customer Consent & Published Updates

If you choose to visit ArkivMusic, you are agreeing to the standards set forth in this Privacy Policy document and in the ArkivMusic Terms & Conditions document. From time to time we may make updates to these documents, which will be accessible from the Privacy Policy and/or the Terms & Conditions links on the bottom of the ArkivMusic home page. If you have any questions or concerns regarding the ArkivMusic Privacy Policy or Terms & Conditions, please contact us at [feedback@arkivmusic.com](mailto:feedback@arkivmusic.com). 

Last updated October 17, 2007.
